infv.com 2010-11-24

# Privacy Policy - infv.com

**Our Privacy Policy**

infv.com, its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering an ad to you, no personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address is collected. However, some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example) are obtained. The information collected are used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, this information may be collected on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, This information may be combined with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.

**Data Collection and Opt Out**

Ads shown on our site, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. These cookies cannot be used to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time an ad is served to you. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps target ads to you. This cookie can help ensure that the same ad will not be served you multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for an ad to be delivered you. If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.

If you have any additional questions about infv.com's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at support@infv.com.

**Advertisers**

**Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**ValueClick Privacy Policies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [here.](http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml)
